[Applause]
most days I'm an actor I'm a fashion
designer but today we're gonna do
something different really different
like egg them different we're gonna help
you sell some insurance seriously no
jokes wanna know how we'll find out how
in just a minute first let's catch the
celebrities in action
you think I'm gonna make just another
sandwich huh
because this is a Sato base lettuce lace
mushroom
double cheese or tomato perfect
[Music]
now that's how I make my perfect
sandwich and just like this sandwich now
you can make your own health insurance
that works for you with future generally
do it yourself health insurance where
you choose what you want or drop what
you don't
oops did you just drop your other
insurance make your choice with future
generally do it yourself health
insurance to get your customized plan
contact our insurance agent from latur
just give a call on 98351-82893
it's a great wardrobe
but not for me because mine should have
a slider for my shoes
a tall rack for my dresses
space for all my purses
[Music]
makeup storage
actually cancel the storage how about a
built-in makeup product
small like my wardrobe and just like
this wardrobe now you can make your own
health insurance that works for you with
future generally do-it-yourself health
insurance
where you choose what you want
or drop what you don't
make your choice with future generally
DIY health insurance to get your
customized plan contact akhil our
insurance agent from local just give a
call on 9351-82893
now comes the best part
you can select any one of these two ads
and make it your own all you have to do
is log on to make your fgad.com choose
between any of the two celebrities and
fill out a brief form with your name
location and mobile number but here's
where it gets really exciting we use Ai
and machine learning to recreate the
celebrities voice and face based on the
information you provide to get your
customized plan contract Priya our
insurance agent from nasik just give a
call on
98351-82893 and contact akhil our
insurance agent from laptop just give a
call on
9351-82893 contact our insurance agent
from Bangalore give a call on
98351-82893 the result
like your customers get a customized
health insurance you get a customized ad
conveniently delivered to you on email
or Whatsapp whichever you prefer a
celebrity promoting your business with a
message that's unique to you will surely
leave your customers in awe and set you
apart from the competition oh wow that
really popular so what are you waiting
for let's get started
[Music]